dsoarhair.com 2019-03-02

# Privacy Policy | DSoar Hair

Your privacy is important to us and we have a responsibility of protecting your personal information. The Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose(under certain conditions) your personal information as well as to secure your personal information. In addition, by visiting the website directly, you will accept the practices described in this Policy.

The Privacy Policy applies to the Site. Don't apply to any offline collection of personal information. Please see details as below.

We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website not operated by DSoar Hair which the Site links or that links to the Site.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

**1\. Information Collection**

We collect information from you in several different ways on Site. The only goal in collecting personal information is to provide an efficient, meaningful and customized experience. For example, we can use personal information to:

· help the site easier to use by not having to enter information more than once.

· help you quickly find information, products, and services.

· create content that is most relevant to you.

· offer you new products information, promotions and services.

(a) Registration and Ordering. Before placing an order, you must complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, you may be asked for the country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. This personal information is used for billing purposes to fulfill orders, communicate you about shipment and internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing order, your personal information would contact you.

(b) Email Addresses. Several locations of Site permit you to enter email address for some purposes including but not limited: to notify you of new brands, new hairstyles, or other new products; or to sign up email newsletters and special offers. 

(c) Cookies and Other Technology. Like many websites, the Site employs cookies and web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation on the Site, recognize you and your access privileges and track your Site usage.

**2\. Information Use**

(a) Internal Use. Using your personal information to process order and provide with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve the Sites' content and layout, outreach, our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you) and determine general market information about visitors to the Site. 

(b) Communications: We can use personal information to communicate with you about the orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register on our Site and a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) You may submit your email address for reasons such as to request for new brands, new product styles, or product sizes; or to sign up for email newsletters and special offers. If you submit your email address, we will deliver the information for you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt-out section as below for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.

**OUR PROMISE OF PRIVACY SECURITY**

We promise that any customer personal information won't purposely be disclosed to the third party.  We try our best to improve the management merchanism and data security system in order to ensure the use accuracy, unauthorized access and secure maintenance of personal information.[  
](file:///C:/Users/Administrator/AppData/Local/youdao/dict/Application/7.1.0.0421/resultui/dict/result.html?keyword=disclosure)

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy from time to time for changed or updated information. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at +86 -15038326555 or admin@dsoarhair.com

 If any question, please contact us.

**Address Information**

 Name: longzhixiang e-commerce business

Address: ROOM 1601, Block 16A, Daxue Kejiyuan(East Disctrict), Dianchang Road, Zhengzhou city of Henan province, China
